Faculty of Business Administration fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Publications, 1970 - 2004; F-42-7; 2.01 m of textual records
  - Departmental publications, 1977 - 2004; F-42-7-1; 38 cm of textual records
    - Employment/Co-op Program, [198-?]; F-42-7-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - Enterprise Centre, [198-?]; F-42-7-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - Small Business Consulting Group (SBCG), [198-?]; F-42-7-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - MBA Executive Program Business Research Monograph #1-3, 1977 - 1980; F-42-7-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - Scholarly Activities Report, 1979 - 1982; F-42-7-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - Executive MBA program, vol. 1, 1980 - 2004; F-42-7-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 42-31)
    - Executive MBA program, vol. 2, 1980 - 2004; F-42-7-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Executive MBA program, vol. 3, 1980 - 2004; F-42-7-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Executive MBA program, vol. 4, 1980 - 2004; F-42-7-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Student Resume Books, 1981 - 1982; F-42-7-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Student Resume Books, 1983 - 1985; F-42-7-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Scholarly Activities Report, 1983 - 1985; F-42-7-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Business Administration workshops and seminars, 1984 - 2002; F-42-7-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - The New Enterprise Program, 1985 - 1987; F-42-7-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Non-profit and Voluntary Sector Management Program, 1985 - 2000; F-42-7-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Scholarly Activities Report, 1986 - 1989; F-42-7-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - Student Resume Books, 1987; F-42-7-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 42-32)
    - MBA Program, 1987 - 2002; F-42-7-1-0-19
    - Foundation Program in Tourism Management, 1988 - 1989; F-42-7-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Foundation Program in Management for Women, 1988 - 2003; F-42-7-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Faculty Profiles and Research Interests, 1989 - 1997; F-42-7-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - FBA "Update", 1989 - 1999; F-42-7-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - FBA Employment and Career Services, [199-]; F-42-7-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Management Information Services Career Handbook, [199-]; F-42-7-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - FBA Administrative Guide, 1990 - 1991; F-42-7-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Scholarly Activities Report, 1990 - 1997; F-42-7-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Strategic Business Practice Program, 1991 - 1992; F-42-7-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - FBA "Accounting Newsletter", 1993; F-42-7-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Undergraduate Student Newsletter "BBA News", 1993 - 1995; F-42-7-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Bachelor of Business Administration, 1994 - 2001; F-42-7-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - MBA Association Student Survival Guide, 1995; F-42-7-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Student Resume Books, 1995; F-42-7-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - MBA Association newsletter "View from the Hill", 1995; F-42-7-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - MBA Association Student Survival Guide, 1996; F-42-7-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Business Administration Student Society (BASS), 1996; F-42-7-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - International Management and Cross-Cultural Communication Program, 1996 - 1997; F-42-7-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Business Administration Student Society Handbook/Directory, 1996 - 2002; F-42-7-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 42-33)
    - Physician's Executive Management Program, 1996 - 2003; F-42-7-1-0-39 (Archival box - small 42-34)
    - Scotiabank resource Centre for Women Entrepreneurs, 1997 - 1998; F-42-7-1-0-40 (Archival box - small 42-34)
    - Graduate Diploma in Business Administration, 1998 - 2000; F-42-7-1-0-41 (Archival box - small 42-34)
    - Scholarly Activities Report, 1998 - 2003; F-42-7-1-0-42 (Archival box - small 42-34)
    - Management of Technology MBA, 2000 - 2002; F-42-7-1-0-43 (Archival box - small 42-34)
    - Management Foundations Development Program, 2003 - 2004; F-42-7-1-0-44 (Archival box - small 42-34)
    - Business Administration Student Society newsletter "Black Ink", 2004; F-42-7-1-0-45 (Archival box - small 42-34)
  - Discussion papers, 1974 - 1985; F-42-7-2; 38 cm of textual records
    - 74-5-2: Male-Female Earnings Differentials in Canada, 1974; F-42-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 76-4-1: Miners and Mining Towns in British Columbia, 1976; F-42-7-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 77-7-2: An Extension of Bayes' Theorum for Act-Conditional States, 1977; F-42-7-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 78-4-2: Allison and UHL Revisited: The Effects of Taste and Brand Name, 1978; F-42-7-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 79-13-2: The Use of Lodging Industry Ratios in Overall Tourism Planning, 1979; F-42-7-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-2-1: Continuous Repair Limit Policies for Vehicle Replacement, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-3-3:Development of Budget Concept in Ottoman Empire 1300-1923, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-4-1: Internal Control for Ottoman Foundations, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-5-1: Sterling: Income Measurement From Financial Statements, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-6-1: Research Sources in Accounting, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-6-3: Behavior Relationship Scales, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-7-3: Small Sample Properties of Regression Estimators, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-10-3: Comparaison D'une Echelle D'evaluation et D'une Echelle de Classement, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-14-3: An Empirical Test of Alt. Procedures for Estimating Market Share, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 80-19-3: Towards a Performance Data and Development System, 1980; F-42-7-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-1-2: Linguistic Usage in Television Advertising, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-1-3: Assessing the Stability of Life-Style Analysis, Without Large Samples, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-2-2: A Tourism Demand Function for the Okanagan, B.C., 1981; F-42-7-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-2-3: Monte Carlo Comparisons of Manova vs. Anova, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-3-2: The Multiplier Impact of Tourist Expenditure in the Okanagan, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-4-1: Manipulation Subjective Expectancy Through Feedback, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-4-2: The Economic Impact of Tourism in Metropolitan Victoria, B.C., 1981; F-42-7-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-5-1: The Launching of Soccer in Vancouver: A Market Definition Study, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-5-2: Effective Interviewing Via the Behavioral Route, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-7-1: Factor Structures of Organizational Climate, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-9-2: The Life Cycle of Consumer Protection in B.C., 1981; F-42-7-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-10-1: Socio-Economic Background, Sex and Pre- Employment, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-11-1: A Comparison of Pre and Post-Employment Work Values, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-12-1: A Comparison of Three Protestant Ethic Scales, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-13-1: Reality Testing of Issues in Organizational Decision-Making, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-14-1: Entries, Exits, and Survival Rates of Businesses Operating in a Northern Community, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-15-1: Factors Affecting the Use of Outplacement by B.C. Firms, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 42-35)
    - 81-16-1: The Use of the Survival Curve in Manpower Planning, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 81-17-1: Labour Turnover: A Case Study, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 81-18-1: A Case Study of the Application of a Terminations Forecast Model, 1981; F-42-7-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-1-1: Preliminary Comparisons of Direct vs. Behavioral Estimation, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-1-3: On the Possibility of a General Theory of Accounting, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-2-1: Good Copy Ain't Necessarily Good English, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-3-1: Multi-Media Instruction in Accounting: A Decade Later, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-3-2: Demand Functions for Hong Kong Tourism, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-3-3: Determination of Tourism Demand for Hawaii Neighbor Islands, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-3-4: Tourism Forecasting: The State-of-the-Art, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-3-5: Predicting Business Failures - A Canadian Approach, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-3-6: Tourism Income Multipliers at the Establishment Level, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 82-3-7: Institutions and Orgs. Engaged in Tourism and Travel Research, 1982; F-42-7-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-1-1: Tourist Income Multipliers for Turkey, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-1-2: Female Stereotyping in Advertising, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-2: One Dimensional Simplex Search, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-1-3: The Emergence of Teaching Assistant Bargaining in Canada, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-3: Differences in Perceptual Patterns of Tourism Impacts, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-4: Three Empirical Tests of the Spatial and Aspatial Theory of Retail Choice, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-4: Lawyers in B.C. Grievance Arbitration, 1981, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-6: B.C.'s Children's Hospital Management of Organizational Change, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-7: An Empirical Analysis of a Proactive Approach to Municipal Referendum Planning, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-8: Estimating the Autocorrelated Error Model with Small Sample Size, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-2-9: Family Decision Making in the Upscale Travel Market, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-3-1: Student's Linguistic Skills and the Language of Television Advertising, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-3-2: The Perceived Impacts of Tourism, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-3-3: Continuous Maturity Diversification of Default-Free Bond Portfolios, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-3-4: On the Interest Rate Parity Theory, Spread and Transaction Costs, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-3-5: Unbiased Estimators of Long-Run Expected Returns Revisited, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 42-36)
    - 83-3-6: Staff Auditor Performance in Public Accounting Firms, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 83-3-7: Resident Opinion of the Effects of Tourism Development in Hawaii, 1983; F-42-7-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 84-1-1: Measurement and Findings on the Perceived Impacts of Tourism, 1984; F-42-7-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 84-1-2: Language Attitudes and Practices of Advertising Agency Personnel, 1984; F-42-7-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 84-1-3: The Language of Advertising, 1984; F-42-7-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 84-1-4: Manpower Systems and Organizational Demography, 1984; F-42-7-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 84-1-5: Monitoring Corporate Financial Health, 1984; F-42-7-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 85-1-1: Electronic Feedback and Energy Consumption, 1985; F-42-7-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 85-2-1: The Long-Term Effects of the Energy Cost Indicator, 1985; F-42-7-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
    - 85-5-1: Advertising Self Regulation: An Analysis of Costs and Benefits, 1985; F-42-7-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 42-37)
  - Student MBA projects, 1970 - 1977; F-42-7-3; 1.25 m of textual records
    - Carr, I.J., [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Cooper, E.W., [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Copping, H.G.A., [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Foran, D.J., [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Malcolm, David Thomas, [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Neale, Geoffrey, [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Paterson, R., [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Watson, John F., [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Westerlund, B.V., [197-?]; F-42-7-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Alexander, B.R., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Ballou, Henry C., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Barnes, Derek, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Clark, William Craig, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Coltman, Michael M., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 42-38)
    - Cote, Paul T., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Culver, Dennis F., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Darc, J., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Graham, Russell Monroe, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Gray, R.E., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Helgeson, David H., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Jobes, Frank A., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Johnson, J.E., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - McDonald, David L., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - McRae, Edward Davidson, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - McRae, Herbert Vaughan, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 42-39)
    - Moloney, John J., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Neylan, F.C.J., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Overholt, Michael J., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Paulson, Gordon R., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Renwick, Robert James, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Roberts, Donald E., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Selby, Joseph C., 1970; F-42-7-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Thykeson, Everett, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Warner, Kenneth Melville, 1970; F-42-7-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Bragg, J.E., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Carey, Neall, 1971; F-42-7-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Croll, John R., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Cronk, Alan Dawson, 1971; F-42-7-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 42-40)
    - Danagher, W.N., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - De Leeuw, Paulus B., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Gray, H.D., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Gray, Ian Alexander, 1971; F-42-7-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Hale, James W., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Hume, H.F., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Iannacone, Ernest M., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Mackay, J.G., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Ross, John Alexander, 1971; F-42-7-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Scott, A.C., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Stinson, D.J.H., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Taillefer, A.E., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Upgaard, E.T., 1971; F-42-7-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Virani, Zinat, 1971; F-42-7-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 42-41)
    - Anderson, F. J. Maxwell, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Bergen, Robert C., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Broadbent, Frank Donald, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Bruins, Gerard, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Chalmers, John David, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Charles, James Thomas, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Chessor, Edward Stanley, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Claridge, R.W., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Curtis, Brian L., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Dunlop, David Whitson Scott, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Ens, Harold Ronald, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Failes, Peter, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Foisy, Maurice Leo, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 42-42)
    - Granholm, Ronald H., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Harris, Peter George, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Hawrysh, Bert Alexander, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Hunt, Anthony Ronald, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Juzkow, Tony Peter, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Kerr, William B.M., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Kloeble, Walter Mathew, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Lawson, Ronald James, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - McClurg, John Matthew, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - O'Connell, Ronald D., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Payne, Ronald David, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-76 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Permack, Harvey Sheldon, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-77 (Archival box - standard 42-43)
    - Powell, John R.P., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-78 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Ritchie, William W., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-79 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Rowe, William John Allan, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-80 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Shamanski, Harvey Raymond, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-81 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Smallridge, Brian Richard, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-82 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Smith, Robin M.R., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-83 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Stuart, Robert Alexander, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-84 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Suzuki, Toshio, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-85 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Tener, David E., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-86 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Warner, D'Arcy William, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-87 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Wighton, James J., 1972; F-42-7-3-0-88 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Yackness, Harmon Barrie, 1972; F-42-7-3-0-89 (Archival box - standard 42-44)
    - Anfield, Frank Arthur, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-90 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Carmichael, J.R., 1973; F-42-7-3-0-91 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Davies, Brian John, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-92 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Ferrie, Adam Ewing John, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-93 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Fricke, John George, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-94 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Gilbert, Philip George, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-95 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Henderson, Norman, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-96 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Hoerber, Gerald Frederic, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-97 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Jarvis, Donald Leslie, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-98 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Kraft, Douglas Roy, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-99 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - Lang, Gordon Keith, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-100 (Archival box - standard 42-45)
    - McAusland, Warren Munroe, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-101 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - McLennan, Robert Purves, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-102 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Mills, Ian Ralph Arthur, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-103 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Ridenour, Larry R., 1973; F-42-7-3-0-104 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Rogers, James Edward, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-105 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Scriabin, Michael, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-106 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Thurston, David, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-107 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Trunkfield, Chris J., 1973; F-42-7-3-0-108 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Wardle, Michael James, 1973; F-42-7-3-0-109 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Henderson, Peter, 1974; F-42-7-3-0-110 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Lissett, A. Peter B., 1974; F-42-7-3-0-111 (Archival box - standard 42-46)
    - Muller, Thomas Edward, 1974; F-42-7-3-0-112 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Nelles, William Allen, 1974; F-42-7-3-0-113 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Nelson, Edward A., 1974; F-42-7-3-0-114 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Turner, Malcolm E., 1974; F-42-7-3-0-115 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Bees, William Duncan, 1975; F-42-7-3-0-116 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Creamer, Carl Clifton, 1975; F-42-7-3-0-117 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Chilvers, Jonathan Paul, 1976; F-42-7-3-0-118 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Dalgleish, Fred R., 1976; F-42-7-3-0-119 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Dane, Leslie H., 1976; F-42-7-3-0-120 (Archival box - standard 42-47)
    - Shutiak, James, 1977; F-42-7-3-0-121 (Archival box - standard 42-47)